In this lesson, we'll use a concepts of regression and
在本课中 我们将重复使用回归和分类
classification repeatedly, so let's first recall their definitions.
的概念 所以让我们先回顾一下它们的定义
A regression model is one that predicts a value like 4 minus 3, or 6.7.
回归模型是一个预测值的模型 例如 4 -3 或 6.7
In the graph on the left, we have gone a line that fits the data closely.
在左边的图表中 我们绘制了一条紧密拟合数据的直线
If we have a new value on the x axis,
如果 x 轴上有一个新值
we approximate by finding the corresponding y value over the line.
则可以在直线上找到相应的 y 值来近似它
A classification problem is when one wants to determine a state,
分类问题主要用来确定状态
such as positive, negative, or such as yes, no, or cat, dog.
例如 正/负 是/否 猫/狗
In the graph in the right, we have some blue points labelled positive and
在右边的图形中 我们有一些蓝色的点 标记为正
some red points labelled negative.
以及一些红色的点 标记为负
And we have drawn a line that separates them.
我们画了一条区分它们的直线
If we have a new value in the plane,
当此平面上有一个新值时
we guess its state based on which of the two regions it belongs.
我们根据它属于这两个区域中的哪一个来猜测它的状态
So to summarize, regression returns a numeric value and
那么总结起来 就是回归返回的是值
classification returns a state.
而分类返回的是状态
So, now that you've built a model, how do you convince yourself and
那么 现在你建好了一个模型 你如何向自己
others that your model is good?
和他人证明这个模型是良好的呢？
You do this by testing.
方法就是测试
So let’s look at the picture of BUFF which shows a small regression example,
我们来看 BUFF 的图片 它显示了一个简单的回归示例
our data corresponds to the grade points.
我们的数据与分数对应
We have trained two models to fit the data.
我们训练了两个模型来拟合该数据
One is a line and the other one is a curve.
一个是直线 另一个是曲线
Now the question is, which of these two models is better?
现在的问题是 这两个模型哪个更好？
Well the one on the right fits the data perfectly,
右边这个完美拟合了数据
while the one on the left doesn't.
而左边这个没有
So we're tempted to say the one on the right.
我们会忍不住说右边的更好
To see how good the fit is we can take a new point, this red point.
要确定拟合性能 我们可以取一个新的点 这个红色点
The point seems to be well approximated by the model in the left, but
左边的模型对这点近似地较好 而右边的
is very badly approximated by the model in the right.
模型近似的效果较差
So it seems that maybe the model in the left is better than the model in
所以最终来看 左侧的模型比
the right, after all.
右边的模型要好
What makes the model in the left better, is that even though it doesn't
左侧模型的优点在于尽管它没有
fit the data perfectly, it generalizes better than the one on the right.
完美拟合数据 但它的泛化能力比右边的好
The model in the right tries to fit the data too well, and
右边的模型太过于完美拟合数据
it ends up memorizing it.
结果将这些数据记了下来
This is called overfitting, and we will learn it later in the nanodegree.
这称为过拟合 我们将在后面的纳米学位课程中学习
Now the question is, how do we find a model that generalizes well?
现在的问题是 我们如何找到一个泛化能力高的模型呢？
This is where we introduce the concept of testing.
在这里 我们就要引入测试的概念
What we'll do here is we'll split our data into two sets, the training set and
我们要在这里做的 是将数据分为两个集合 一个是训练集
the testing set.
一个测试集
In this figure the training set is the set of grey points, and
在这个图中 训练集是灰色点的集合
the testing set is the set of white points.
测试集是白色点的集合
And now what we'll do is as the name suggests, we'll use a training set to
接下来 顾名思义 我们要用训练集
train the model, and then we test our results in the testing set.
来训练模型 然后在测试集中测试结果
So, here we have two copies of our sets to the training set formed by the gray
现在我们有两个数据集 由灰色点组成的训练集
points and the testing set formed by the white points.
和用白色点组成的测试集
We can see two models that we train on the training set, the gray points.
可以看到训练了训练集的模型 即灰色点
Here the model on the right seems to be better than the model on the left.
右边的模型看起来似乎比左边的模型好
But once we test on the testing set, the white points, we see that the model
但是一旦我们在测试集上测试 即白色点 可以看到
on the left is much better, as the errors in red are much smaller.
左侧的模型更好 因为红色所表示的误差更小
Thus we conclude that the model on the left is better.
因此可以得出结论 左侧的模型更好
Because although it performs a little less well on the training set,
因为虽然它在训练集上的表现略弱
it does much better on the testing set.
但它在测试集上的效果更好
We can do the same procedure on a classification problem such as the one
我们可以将相同的过程用于分类问题 就像这里的
here.
这个
We have trained two classification models to separate the blue positive and
我们训练了两个分类模型来分离蓝正点
the red negative points.
和红负点
This one on the left is okay, as it only makes a few mistakes.
左边的这个模型还好 因为它仅犯了少数几个错误
This one on the right does great,
右侧的这个非常棒
because it manages to separate all the points.
因为它准确区分了所有的点
But our intuition tells us that the one left may be better,
但直觉告诉我们左边的可能更好
as it is more general.
因为它更泛化
Meanwhile, the model in the left treats these outliers as noise, and
同时 左边的模型将这些异常数值视为噪声
it tries to fit the data in a simpler and more general way.
并尝试以更简单和更一般的方式来拟合数据
So in order to pick a good model, we'll take some points and
所以为了挑选一个好的模型 我们需要取一些点
call them the testing set.
称之为测试集
The training set is then given by the points that are filled in,
那么 训练集用实心点表示
while the testing set is given by the points that are not filled in.
测试集用空心点表示
Now we train the two models.
现在我们训练这两个模型
Notice that the two models fit the training set well.
注意这两个点对训练集的拟合都不错
But once we introduce the testing set, the model in the left
但当我们引入测试集 左边的模型
only makes one mistake, whereas the model in the right makes two mistakes.
仅有一处错误 而右边的点有两处错误
Thus by testing we conclude that the model in the left is better.
因此 通过测试 我们得出结论左边的模型更好
The way to do this in scikit-learn is very simple using
在 sklearn 中这样做的方式很简单 使用
the function train-test-split from the model selection package.
模型选择包中的 train-test-split 函数即可
First, we import train_test_split.
首先 我们导入 train_test_split
The train_test_split function takes the following as arguments.
train_test_split 函数将以下作为参数
The input, the output, and
输入、输出以及
the percentage of data we want to leave as testing data.
我们想留作测试数据的数据比例
For example, test size equals 0.25 means that 25 percent of our
例如 test_size 等于 0.25 指将我们 25% 的数据
data will be used as testing.
用作测试集
In this example, we have 16 data points.
在这个例子中 我们有 16 个数据点
So 4 of them will be used as testing data, and
所以其中 4 个将用作测试数据
the remaining 12 as training data.
而剩下的 12 个用作训练数据
Now there is a golden rule that we must never, ever break.
有一条黄金法则我们永远都不能违背
The rule says, thou shalt never use your testing data for training.
那就是 不能将测试数据用于训练
This is very important when we select some data for
这一点非常重要 当我们选择一些数据用于
testing, we must put it aside, and not look at it until the very end.
测试时 必须将它们放在一边 直到最后一步再用
And we should not use it to train the algorithm.
而且我们不能使用它们来训练模型
This rule is actually very easy to accidentally break, and
如果不注意 我们很容易违反它
you'll see why very soon.
你很快就会知道是怎么回事